Guide to the Feminist Women's Health Center Records, 1973-2003 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Clinic Files Series, 1980-2002 and undated, (29 boxes)
  - Patient Education Information, undated, (2 boxes)
    - Anesthesia information (Box 47)
    - Appreciation note (Box 47)
    - Artificial insemination information (Box 47)
    - Authorization and consent (Box 47)
    - Authorization and consent for abortion by dilation and evacuation (Box 47)
    - Bacterial vaginosis (Box 47)
    - Birth control guide (Box 47)
    - Birth control history (Box 47)
    - Birth control pill consent form (Box 47)
    - Birth control- male (Box 47)
    - Birth control- guide to the methods (Box 47)
    - Birth control pill instructions (Box 47)
    - Birth control pill and women over 40 (Box 47)
    - Breast cancer/exam (Box 47)
    - Breast self exam (Box 47)
    - CPR (Box 47)
    - Cervical cap information sheet (Box 47)
    - Cervical cap consent form (Box 47)
    - Cervical cancer/Pap smear (Box 47)
    - Cervical osmotic dilator insertion notes (Box 47)
    - Change of prognosis (Box 47)
    - Chlamydia (Box 47)
    - Chronology of health concerns (Box 47)
    - Colposcopy/biopsy consent form (Box 47)
    - Common vaginal and gynecological conditions (Box 47)
    - Condoms and foam consent/condom information (Box 47)
    - Crabs (Box 47)
    - Cytomegalovirus (Box 47)
    - Depo-Provera consent (Box 47)
    - Depo-Provera information sheet (Box 47)
    - Digoxin consent (Box 47)
    - Diaphragm consent (Box 47)
    - Diaphragm information sheet (Box 47)
    - Diagnostic sonogram referrals (Box 47)
    - Drug information (Box 47)
    - Dysplasia (Box 47)
    - Early abortion information sheet (Box 47)
    - Emergency contraception (Box 47)
    - Emergency contraception consent form and patient instruction sheet (Box 47)
    - Endometrial biopsy informed consent (Box 47)
    - Fibroid fact sheet (Box 47)
    - Fibroid information (Box 47)
    - Flu vaccine consent and information (Box 47)
    - Gonorrhea (Box 47)
    - Hepatitis B (Box 47)
    - Herbal abortion (Box 47)
    - Herpes (Box 47)
    - HIV/hepatitis B needle stick consent (Box 47)
    - Home birth referral information (Box 47)
    - Human Papillomavirus (HPV) (Box 47)
    - Intrauterine Device (IUD) information (Box 47)
    - Lactation information (Box 47)
    - Laminaria agreement (Box 47)
    - Laminaria insertion (Box 47)
    - Laminaria instructions for clients (Box 47)
    - Lesbian health care concerns (Box 47)
    - Lesbian health packet (Box 47)
    - Lunelle injection (Box 47)
    - Mammogram information (Box 47)
    - Medical abortion (Box 48)
    - Menopause (Box 48)
    - Menstrual cramps (Box 48)
    - Menstrual extraction (ME) (Box 48)
    - Menstrual record chart (Box 48)
    - National Abortion Federation fact sheets (Box 48)
    - Natural birth control (Box 48)
    - Negative-positive test explanation sheet (Box 48)
    - Newsletters (Box 48)
    - Non-specific vaginitis information sheet (Box 48)
    - Norplant (Box 48)
    - Oral consent form (Box 48)
    - Pap smear results (Box 48)
    - Patient survey (Box 48)
    - Perimenopause (Box 48)
    - PMS- answers at last (Box 48)
    - Pregnancy screening results information (Box 48)
    - Premarital blood testing client consent form (Box 48)
    - Prenatal care and delivery referrals (Box 48)
    - Referral book information (Box 48)
    - Referral list (Box 48)
    - RH-negative blood and Rhogam (Box 48)
    - Scabies (Box 48)
    - Scant tissue information (Box 48)
    - Second trimester referrals (Box 48)
    - Self-examination using the plastic speculum (Box 48)
    - Sickle cell disease (Box 48)
    - Sickle cell anemia (Box 48)
    - Sickle cell trait (Box 48)
    - Sickle cell and the Pill (Box 48)
    - Syphilis (Box 48)
    - Trichomonas (Box 48)
    - Trichomonas- Flagyl question (Box 48)
    - Vaginitis (Box 48)
    - (Vietnamese) health history (Box 48)
    - (Vietnamese) after care instructions (Box 48)
    - Well-Woman consent form (Box 48)
    - General information (Box 48)
    - Abortion (Box 48)
    - Birth control (Box 48)
    - Miscellaneous drug information/fact sheets, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Safe methods of birth control (Box 48)
    - Fact sheets (Box 48)
    - Oral contraceptives (Box 48)
    - Lesbian and gay friendly referrals (Box 48)
    - Atlanta resources for HIV/AIDS, 1995, 1997 (Box 48)
    - HIV materials (Box 48)
    - HIV/AIDS information, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 48)
- Subject Files Series, 1977-2003, (23 boxes)
  Includes files maintained by the staff of the Feminist Women's Health Center on a range of topics related to women's health issues, events, local information, and other women's health clinics.
  This series contains two subseries: a General subseries which covers these subjects broadly, and an Anti-Abortion Violence subseries which focuses specifically on anti-abortion protests at the FWHC and other locations, the anti-abortion movement in the United States, and pro-choice efforts to counter this movement.
  - Anti-Abortion Violence, 1985-1991, (7 boxes)
    Contains files documenting acts of violence perpetrated against the FWHC, protests held at the FWHC, and court cases related to anti-abortion violence at the FWHC and at other clinics nationwide. Also includes information about anti-abortion groups and individuals which was collected by the FWHC, training information for clinic staff and volunteers about handling anti-abortion incidents and protesters, and photographs of anti-abortion activists both at the FWHC and at other locations so that FWHC staff might recognize them. Some materials in this subseries have been redacted or relocated to the Closed Series.
    - Operation Rescue (OR)- general information pre-Atlanta (Box 49)
    - Planned Parenthood- background on OR (Box 49)
    - Chronology of OR actions (Box 49)
    - OR arrests, 1988 Oct 4 (Box 49)
    - Photographs: Atlanta, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Log of anti-abortion presence at Feminist Women's Health Center, 1989 (Box 49)
    - OR return engagement, 1989 Dec (Box 49)
    - Anti abortion activity at FWHC- tape transcription, 1989 Dec 27 (Box 49)
    - Police report- arrests at Dr. Gay's, 1989 Dec 29 (Box 49)
    - Police reports and summons, 1989 (Box 49)
    - Log of anti-abortion presence at FWHC, 1990 (Box 49)
    - OR arrests at FWHC, 1990 Jan (Box 49)
    - OR arrests AWMC, 1990 Jan 17 (Box 49)
    - OR arrests FWHC, 1990 Feb (Box 49)
    - OR Atlanta mailing, 1990 Mar (Box 49)
    - OR arrests FWHC, 1990 Mar 21 (Box 49)
    - OR arrests FWHC, 1990 Mar 27 (Box 49)
    - OR Atlanta SurgiCenter invasion, 1990 May 15 (Box 49)
    - Anti-abortion log, 1991 (Box 49)
    - Photographs, 1991 Jun 12 (Box 49)
    - Photographs, 1991 Jun 21 (Box 49)
    - OR arrests Youth for America, 1991 Jul 30 (Box 49)
    - Arrest, 1991 Sept 4 (Box 49)
    - OR arrests, 1991 Oct 22 (Box 49)
    - OR Wichita, 1991 (Box 49)
    - OR investigation (Box 49)
    - Rescue news brief (Box 49)
    - OR media coverage in Los Angeles (Box 49)
    - National coverage of OR (Box 49)
    - International media coverage (Box 49)
    - National Right to Life (Box 49)
    - Trials from OR arrests in Atlanta- news coverage (Box 49)
    - OR national media coverage of Atlanta, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Randall Terry/OR (Box 49)
    - OR demonstration at Atlanta Journal-Constitution (AJC), 1990 May 19 (Box 49)
    - OR media- Randall Terry out of jail, 1990 (Box 49)
    - OR, abortion, anti-abortion news articles (Box 49)
    - OR local media coverage (Box 49)
    - Operation Rescue injunction (Box 50)
    - Operation Rescue v. Alexandria (Box 50)
    - NOW, City of New York v. Randall Terry (Box 50)
    - Atlanta v. OR trial preparation (Box 50)
    - Atlanta v. OR direct testimony of Lynn Randall (Box 50)
    - Atlanta v. Operation Rescue (Box 50)
    - Defendant information (Box 50)
    - Background information OR defendants arrested at FWHC (Box 50)
    - City of Atlanta v. Operation Rescue article on Judge Frank Hull (Box 50)
    - City of Atlanta v. Operation Rescue (Box 50)
    - Atlanta v. Operation Rescue appeal (Box 50)
    - Snuggs v. Denson- city's response (Box 50)
    - Complaint re: Susan Snuggs (Box 50)
    - Anti-abortion activity S. Snuggs arrest, 1988 Nov 11 (Box 50)
    - CA injunction on Operation Rescue (Box 50)
    - National Lawyers' Guild- injunction update (Box 50)
    - Ardia v. Operation Rescue (Box 50)
    - RICO information (Box 50)
    - Mother Jones article on Randall Terry (Box 50)
    - Operation Rescue on Randall Terry- San Jose News (Box 50)
    - Randall Terry's probation orders Fulton County (Box 50)
    - OR police reports (Box 50)
    - OR legal (Box 50)
    - Operation Rescue Atlanta police (Box 50)
    - Operation Rescue attorney fees (Box 50)
    - Operation Rescue NAF guidelines (Box 50)
    - Letter re: injunction (Box 50)
    - Injunction press coverage (Box 50)
    - Copy of injunction and resolution Operation Rescue (Box 50)
    - Injunction status report, 1991 (Box 50)
    - Legal materials, OR litigation, 1989-1990 (Box 50)
    - OR Refuse and Resist organizing material (Box 50)
    - Prisoners of Christ (Box 50)
    - Rutherford Institute, Georgia (Box 50)
    - Operation Rescue- outline for Womancare presentation (Box 50)
    - OR strategy meeting, Planned Parenthood Federation of America (PPFA) (Box 50)
    - Luis Vasquez (Box 50)
    - Clinic violence, clippings, and articles (Box 50)
    - Stress questionnaire re: OR and anti- activity (Box 51)
    - Picketing questionnaire (Box 51)
    - Operation Rescue client questionnaire (Box 51)
    - The Spirit of '76 and other threats, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - OR literature order blanks (Box 51)
    - Rescue report (Box 51)
    - Ode to Operation Rescue (Box 51)
    - OR advertisement in AJC, 1988 Sept 7 (Box 51)
    - Anti-abortion flyers (Box 51)
    - OR pamphlet- Return to Atlanta, 1989 Dec 15 (Box 51)
    - OR pamphlets (Box 51)
    - OR mailings from Randall Terry (Box 51)
    - Terry's letter from Fulton County Jail, 1989 Oct (Box 51)
    - Letter from Randall Terry, 1990 Apr (Box 51)
    - OR brochure/letter, 1990 Feb (Box 51)
    - City of Atlanta (Box 51)
    - Operation Rescue- NYC (Box 51)
    - OR civil rights comparison (Box 51)
    - Operation Rescue legal material (Box 51)
    - Denial of McMonagle appeal- Georgia Court of Appeals (Box 51)
    - Escort coordinator logs (Box 51)
    - Operation Rescue newsletter (Box 51)
    - OR Atlanta office (Box 51)
    - Operation Rescue support letters (Box 51)
    - Operation Rescue: our fundraiser for FWHC (Box 51)
    - Operation Rescue letters to city council re: injunction (Box 51)
    - Letters to police (Box 51)
    - The Victim Souls for the Unborn Christ Child (Box 52)
    - Scheidler, Joseph (Box 52)
    - NOW v. Scheidler (Box 52)
    - Scheidler- Atlanta, 1986 Jan (Box 52)
    - Scheidler's visit, 1987 Apr (Box 52)
    - Operation Rescue NYC- Scheidler, 1988 (Box 52)
    - PLAN convention Chicago, 1988 (Box 52)
    - Williams, Mitchell appeal to Supreme Court (Box 52)
    - Youth for America (Box 52)
    - FWHC v. Williams (Box 52)
    - Adopt-a-Picketer program (Box 52)
    - Atlanta Coalition for Life (Box 52)
    - Video log, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Tape transcription (Box 52)
    - Anti-activity chronology, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Picketers (Box 52)
    - Home picketing (Box 52)
    - Affidavits- staff and escorts (Box 52)
    - Client questionnaires (Box 52)
    - Anti-abortion activity FWHC by tape (Box 52)
    - Anti-abortion information (Box 52)
    - Anti-abortion mail (Box 52)
    - Anti-abortion literature, All About Issues (Box 52)
    - Abortion- Post-abortion syndrome (Box 52)
    - Anti-abortion mailings (Box 52)
    - Women Exploited by Abortion (WEBA) (Box 52)
    - FWHC v. Williams affidavits (Box 52)
    - Williams, Mitchell, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Anti-abortion literature (Box 53)
    - Anti-abortion attorneys (Box 53)
    - Anti-abortion activity- Atlanta (Box 53)
    - ATF (Box 53)
    - Atlanta Care Center (Box 53)
    - Atlanta police phone numbers (Box 53)
    - Atlanta police meetings, correspondence (Box 53)
    - Atlanta Pro-Choice Action Committee (Box 53)
    - Atlanta Christian Newspaper- Love 86 Express (Box 53)
    - Anti's cars (Box 53)
    - Black et al v. City of Atlanta (Box 53)
    - Christian Activist for Life League (Box 53)
    - NOW- Project Stand Up for Women clinic defense (Box 53)
    - Clinic defense- legal (Box 53)
    - Escort guidelines (Box 53)
    - Operation Rescue general correspondence (Box 53)
    - Operation Rescue Anti's letter to mayor (Box 53)
    - Atlanta phone log tape transcripts (Box 53)
    - OR message log, 1989-1990 (Box 53)
    - Operation Rescue Rev. Stanley dispute with OR (Box 53)
    - Falwell's support of OR (Box 53)
    - Anti- propaganda (Box 53)
    - Operation Rescue Atlanta notes (Box 53)
    - Emergency phone list Operation Rescue (Box 53)
    - OR T-shirt (Box 53)
    - Articles on clinic violence (Box 54)
    - Clinic violence (Box 54)
    - Photographs (Box 54)
    - Clinic violence training packet (Box 54)
    - Clinic violence incident reporting form (Box 54)
    - Spray paint vandalism, 1989 Apr 28 (Box 54)
    - Pensacola, Florida clinic bombers media coverage (Box 54)
    - Georgia Nurses for Life (Box 54)
    - Georgia Right to Life (Box 54)
    - Free speech advocates (Box 54)
    - Northside Women's Clinic v. Chamblee (Box 54)
    - Girl vigilantes (Box 54)
    - Holy terror (Box 54)
    - City of Atlanta injunction- Georgia Supreme Court decision (Box 54)
    - Preliminary injunction (Box 54)
    - Injunction- contempt citations (Box 54)
    - Injunction- contempt charges (Box 54)
    - Newspaper clippings on anti-abortion protests, FWHC and national, 1988 Jul-1989 Mar (Box 54)
    - Anti-abortion propaganda (Box 54)
    - Major anti-abortion groups list (Box 54)
    - Articles (Box 54)
    - Escort responsibilities and guidelines (Box 54)
    - Security information (Box 54)
    - Basic FYI (Box 54)
    - Anti- activity log, 1990 (Box 54)
    - Photos of Luis Vasquez et al, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - Photo album, 1990 (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous FWHC articles/information, (4 folders) (Box 55)
  - General Subject Files, 1977-2003, (17 boxes)
    Contains files, clippings, and newsletters related to women's health, events, local information, other women's health clinics, and issues such as parental notification.
    Original order and folder titles have been retained in most cases; there are clusters of folders with similar subject matter or dates of creation. Some files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Injunction (Box 55, continued)
    - Referral source contacts, 1991 (Box 55, continued)
    - Brochures, etc. from referral visits, 1991 (Box 55, continued)
    - Upcoming projects, 1991 (Box 55, continued)
    - Art project- Lindy Russell, Bonnie Cramer (Box 55, continued)
    - Rolodex cards, 1991 (Box 55, continued)
    - Public speaking workshop, 1991 Oct 17 (Box 55, continued)
    - New South Directory (progressive organizations) (Box 55, continued)
    - "I Can Help" forms (Box 55, continued)
    - Abortion price forms, 1991 Sept (Box 55, continued)
    - D&E services insert, 1991 (Box 55, continued)
    - Caldex cards, 1991 (Box 55, continued)
    - Open house (Box 55, continued)
    - Georgia College health fair, 1991 May 1 (Box 55, continued)
    - Yellow Pages, Georgia (Box 55, continued)
    - Yellow Pages, South Carolina (Box 55, continued)
    - Yellow Pages, Alabama, 1992 (Box 55, continued)
    - Yellow Pages, Montgomery, Alabama, 1993 (Box 55, continued)
    - Microscope collom (Box 55, continued)
    - T-shirts and buttons ordering, 1991 July (Box 55, continued)
    - Other Abortion Yellow Pages (Box 56)
    - Upcoming Yellow Pages (Box 56)
    - Atlanta Journal-Constitution, 1990-1991 (Box 56)
    - Macon Telegraph and News (Box 56)
    - Athens Red & Black (Box 56)
    - Southern Voice, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Advertising budget, 1991 (Box 56)
    - Civil Pages Ltd., 1992 (Box 56)
    - General services brochure, 1992/Abortion tear sheet, 1992 (Box 56)
    - FWHC services brochure (Box 56)
    - FWHC Board meeting notes, 1990 Nov 26 (Box 56)
    - OR tape transcripts, 1989 Dec 28-1990 Jun 2 (Box 56)
    - Notes for IRS manual (Box 56)
    - Europe (Box 56)
    - Kim Thomas' murder (Box 56)
    - Escort/clinic defense information (Box 56)
    - Atlanta AIDS Network, 1990 (Box 56)
    - APAC Information, 1990/COOR Info, 1990 (Box 56)
    - New services- physician's letter, 1990 Oct (Box 56)
    - Newsletter projection, 1990 (Box 56)
    - Grandmother ad (Box 56)
    - Monthly meeting notes, 1990 (Box 56)
    - Holiday stickers, 1990 (Box 56)
    - Abortion statistics, DHS, 1987 (Box 56)
    - ME- FDA (Box 56)
    - ME articles, 1989-1990 (Box 56)
    - "When Does Life Begin," Psychology Today, 1989 Sept (Box 56)
    - San Francisco Chronicle article on Womancare, 1991 Jul 2 (Box 56)
    - RCAR Information (Box 56)
    - NARAL Information (Box 56)
    - GARAL Public Service Announcement (PSA) (Box 56)
    - Abortion research papers (Box 56)
    - Clinic violence (NAF), 1990 (Box 56)
    - Clinic violence, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Anti-abortion violence, 1977-1987 (Box 56)
    - Why Do Christians Use Birth Control- Randall Terry article, 1991 (Box 56)
    - Fundraising workshop, 1989 Dec (Box 56)
    - Benefit press release, 1990 Jan 22 (Box 56)
    - Roe v. Wade fundraiser, 1990 (Box 56)
    - Operation Oppress-You, 1990 (Box 56)
    - Men's Coalition for Reproductive Choice (Box 56)
    - Horizon Theater benefit performance (Box 56)
    - Jesse Helms information, 1990 Oct (Box 56)
    - OR literature, media coverage, 1990-1991 (Box 56)
    - Emory University course: Quest for Excellence in Reproductive Health, 1997 (Box 56)
    - Anti literature handed out at clinics (Box 57)
    - Parental notification- US Supreme Court, 1990/Georgia statute, 1991 (Box 57)
    - NAF anti-violence totals, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Anti-abortion activity, 1991 (Box 57)
    - OR in Wichita, Summer 1991 (Box 57)
    - Title X- gag rule (Box 57)
    - APAC proposed band benefit, 1991 Mar 10 (Box 57)
    - Griffith Youth Health Expo, 1991 Aug (Box 57)
    - Visitors, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Orders for safe sex guide/speculums, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Log of information packets sent out, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Speaking engagements, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Monthly meeting notes, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Request for information/brochures log (Box 57)
    - FWHC business and fee cards (Box 57)
    - Planned Parenthood materials, 1992 (Box 57)
    - Life in Hell cartoon (Box 57)
    - NAF ordering information (Box 57)
    - Choice- NARAL (Box 57)
    - Issues in Brief- Alan Guttmacher Institute (Box 57)
    - No Going Back WBFC (Box 57)
    - Attitudes toward abortion (Box 57)
    - Civil rights OR letter (Box 57)
    - NARAL "Voices of Women" ordering information (Box 57)
    - Cinema Guild, Holy Terror, Abortion N&S (Box 57)
    - Girl vigilantes/Luis Vasquez (Box 57)
    - Statements/pictures of injunctions violations (Box 57)
    - Athens Observer, 1991 (Box 57)
    - "My Grandmother" ad (Box 57)
    - Gwinnett Daily News (Box 57)
    - UGA college directory/W. Georgia college directory (Box 57)
    - Atlanta Women's News (Box 57)
    - Footnotes, 1990 (Box 57)
    - Alternatives information, 1992 (Box 57)
    - Dahlonega Yellow Pages, 1989 (Box 57)
    - Atlanta Journal/Constitution (Box 57)
    - Current advertising, 1989-1990 (Box 57)
    - Athens Observer, Fall 1989 (Box 57)
    - Atlanta 9 to 5 (Box 57)
    - Advertising budget, 1990 (Box 57)
    - Smyrna Yellow Pages, 1989 (Box 57)
    - Greenville Yellow Pages, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Women's Yellow Pages, 1991-1992 (Box 57)
    - Georgia Woman (Box 57)
    - College paper ads, 1992: Georgia Tech, Agnes Scott, Emory (Box 57)
    - Bell South Gainesville, Feb 1991-1992 (Box 57)
    - Athens Yellow Pages, 1991-1992 (Box 57)
    - Calhoun County, Alabama 1991 Yellow Pages (Box 57)
    - Advertising from Tom Tortorici (Box 57)
    - Women's Heath Watch- FWHC newsletter (Box 57)
    - FWHC newsletter, 1989 (Box 57)
    - Newsletter, Spring 1990 (Box 57)
    - Newsletter, Fall 1990 (Box 57)
    - Georgia Tech University directories, 1989 (Box 57)
    - Current ads, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Atlanta Yellow Pages, 1988 (Box 57)
    - Bell South- Athens, 1988 (Box 57)
    - Ms. Magazine special report on abortion, 1995 (Box 57)
    - Atlanta Yellow Pages, 1989 (Box 58)
    - Bell South- Albany, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Macon Yellow Pages, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Calhoun County, Ala. Yellow Pages, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Southern Bell, 1988 Jun (Box 58)
    - Bell South- Gainesville, 1989 (Box 58)
    - Yellow Pages- outlying areas, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Atlanta Yellow Pages, 1990-1991 (Box 58)
    - Atlanta Yellow Pages, 1991-1992 (Box 58)
    - The Red and Black, 1987 (Box 58)
    - Bell South- Albany, 1991-1992 (Box 58)
    - Greenville Yellow Pages, 1991-1992 (Box 58)
    - Creative Loafing ad, 1989-1990 (Box 58)
    - Minors and abortion (Box 58)
    - Mortality rate- abortion (Box 58)
    - NAF's Amicus Curiae (Box 58)
    - Parental and spousal consent (Box 58)
    - Pro-choice articles (Box 58)
    - Public health and abortion (Box 58)
    - States' anti-abortion legislation (Box 58)
    - Chapter 290-5-33: Ambulatory Surgical Treatment Centers (Box 58)
    - D&E Regulations, 1983: Chapter 290-5-32 (Box 58)
    - Georgia Administrative Procedures Act (Box 58)
    - Community relations monthly reports, 1983 (Box 58)
    - Ad examples, 1984 (Box 58)
    - FWHC visitors, 1989 (Box 58)
    - FWHC visitors, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Yellow Pages- outlying areas, 1991 (Box 58)
    - Bell South- Athens, 1989 (Box 58)
    - Yellow Pages- outlying areas, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Yellow Pages - outlying areas, 1987 (Box 58)
    - Feminist Women's Health 580 14th St NW (Box 58)
    - Bell South- Columbus, 1987-1988 (Box 58)
    - Bell South- Macon, 1987-1989 (Box 58)
    - Spelman Spotlight, 1988 (Box 58)
    - Neighbor newspapers (Box 58)
    - Out of the Sky- Macon Free Weekly (Box 58)
    - Abortion provider public relations- NAF Feminist Caucus, 1990 (Box 58)
    - Accounting codes (Box 58)
    - Ad- Observer (Box 58)
    - Ad material (Box 58)
    - Phone company- ads (Box 58)
    - Adoption (Box 58)
    - Films on reproductive rights (Box 58)
    - Fundraising list, 1989 (Box 58)
    - Fundraiser originals, Summer 1983 (Box 58)
    - Guttmacher Institute price lists- publications (Box 58)
    - M.E. video (Box 58)
    - Anti-abortion movement (Box 58)
    - Funding (Box 58)
    - GA 1973 abortion law (Box 58)
    - History of abortion (Box 58)
    - Medicaid and abortion, 1984 (Box 58)
    - "Midtrimester Abortion" (Box 58)
    - National Abortion Federation meeting, 1993 (Box 58)
    - Brochures (Box 59)
    - Other women's health centers (Box 59)
    - Center for Black Woman's Wellness (Box 59)
    - Eastern Women's Center (Box 59)
    - Winnipeg Women's Health Center (Box 59)
    - Medical facility brochures (Box 59)
    - Women's clinics in Georgia (Box 59)
    - Women's clinics outside Georgia (Box 59)
    - The Hope Clinic for Women, Ltd. (Box 59)
    - Reproductive Health Services (Box 59)
    - Newsletter, Summer/Fall 1991 (Box 59)
    - Newsletter, Spring 1991 (Box 59)
    - Newsletter, Summer 1992 (Box 59)
    - Copies of newsletters (Box 59)
    - Office business (Box 59)
    - Battery charger instructions (Box 59)
    - Wolf camera- warranty (Box 59)
    - Nikon Teletouch camera instructions (Box 59)
    - OSHA (Box 59)
    - FWHC Board, 1989-1990 (Box 59)
    - RU-486 (Box 59)
    - National Abortion Federation seminar, risk management, 1997 (Box 59)
    - International Women's Health Coalition (Box 60)